seo-training-course.com 2019-03-04

# eMarketing University Privacy Policy

Last Revision: May 23, 2018

eMarketing University (hereinafter "University") is strictly committed to the privacy of its customers. University shall take all reasonable measures to protect your personal information. 

This Privacy Policy covers how University uses personal information that users provide to University when they use the eMarketing University (hereinafter "Service"). By using the Service you accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. 

## How We Collect and Use Your Information

You can browse the Service website (hereinafter "Website") located at [http://www.seo-training-course.com](http://www.seo-training-course.com/) without providing any personal information. To start using the Service you are required to order a Service product and provide some personal information. 

University collects the Personal Information and Anonymous Information about you. Personal Information is the information that identifies you as a person, for example your name, mailing address, email address and payment details. Anonymous Information refers to information that does not identify a specific individual. 

## Personal Information

We collect your name, email address, postal address, phone number and credit card details when you order the Service products. We may use your Personal Information to bill you for the Service products and other charges. Billing is performed by a third-party billing service that meets Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards securing your sensitive financial and billing information. We may also use your Personal Information to respond to an email or other inquiry or request, to help improve the Service, to customize your experience at the Website or to send updates or notices about the Service. 

## Anonymous Information

Every time you visit the Website, University saves your IP address, the name and IP address of a remote host computer, time, status and amount of transferred data, the website from which you entered the Service Website and the product and release data of your web browser in a log file. University uses the data from this log file in anonymous form without reference to your Personal Information for aggregated demographic and/or geographic statistics. Using the log file, University can also identify defects in the Service and thus continually improve the quality of the Service. 

## Cookies

As is common practice with almost all professional websites and services, the Website uses cookies. A cookie is a small data file that is stored on a user’s computer to enable the Service to recognize a user that previously used the Service. This chapter describes what information they gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. You can change the settings of your web browser to refuse cookies and to remove them from your computer. However, some features of the Services may not function properly without cookies.

For more general information on cookies, see the Wikipedia article on HTTP Cookies: <https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie>

Cookies are also the cornerstone for any web analytics solution that tracks interaction between a browser and a website. University uses information collected from cookies to track the pages of the Website that our users view, the browsers they use and other information about user activity when visiting the Website.

We utilize Google Analytics, a web analysis service provided by Google, to better understand your use of our Website and Service. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit the Website, what pages they visit and what other sites they used prior to visiting. Google uses the data collected to track and examine the use of the Website to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected on the Website to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. University implements the Remarketing with Google Analytics for Display Advertising online. University and the third-party vendors, including Google Inc., use the first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on a person's past visits to the Website. As a result, University’s ads shall be displayed on the sites across the Web. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the Ads Preferences Manager. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Website is restricted by the [Google Analytics Terms of Use](https://www.google.com/analytics/terms/us.html) and the [Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/). Google offers an opt-out mechanism for the web available [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/). 

If you are subscribed to the Service and you wish to log in to your Service account, your Web browser must accept cookies. A cookie/session variable is assigned to you when you log in, and is placed on your computer for programming purposes only. It ensures that you have properly logged in and that your personal information is only accessible to you. The Web browser's settings can be customized to refuse cookies and to remove them from your computer.

## How We Use Cookies

Our website, like many others, stores and retrieves information on your browser using cookies. We use cookies for a variety of reasons detailed below. Unfortunately, in most cases there are no industry standard options for disabling cookies without completely disabling the functionality and features they add to this site. It is recommended that you leave all cookies on if you are not sure whether you need them or not in case they are used to provide a service that you use.

**Necessary** cookies help make a website usable by enabling basic functions like page navigation and access to secure areas of the website. The website cannot function properly without these cookies: 

  * **PHPSESSID** cookie preserves user session state across page requests and is stored during a session.

**Statistic** cookies help website owners to understand how visitors interact with websites by collecting and reporting information anonymously:

  * **__utm.gif** -Google Analytics Tracking Code that logs details about the visitor's browser and computer and is stored during a session;
  * **__utma** collects data on the number of times a user has visited the website as well as dates for the first and most recent visit. Used by Google Analytics and is stored during 2 years; 
  * **__utmb** registers a timestamp with the exact time of when the user accessed the website. Used by Google Analytics to calculate the duration of a website visit and is stored during a session; 
  * **__utmc** registers a timestamp with the exact time of when the user leaves the website. Used by Google Analytics to calculate the duration of a website visit. Is is stored during a session;
  * **__utmt** used to throttle the speed of requests to the server and is stored during a session;
  * **__utmz** collects data on where the user came from, what search engine was used, what link was clicked and what search term was used. Used by Google Analytics. Initiator: Script tag, page source line number 93. Source: https://www.google-analytics.com/ga.j. It’s stored during 6 months.

**Marketing** cookies are used to track visitors across websites. The intention is to display ads that are relevant and engaging for the individual user and thereby more valuable for publishers and third party advertisers:

  * **ads/conversion/#** used to track conversions and is stored during a session;
  * **IDE** used by Google DoubleClick to register and report the website user's actions after viewing or clicking one of the advertiser's ads with the purpose of measuring the efficacy of an ad and to present targeted ads to the user. It is stored for 1 year;
  * **test_cookie** used to check if the user's browser supports cookies and is stored during a session. 

To refuse Google Analytics cookies, click on the relevant opt-out link:[Google Analytics](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)

## How We Share Your Information

Privacy of our users is very important for University. We shall not disclose, sell or rent your Personal Information to any third party for marketing purposes. We shall share your Personal Information with the third parties only if you instruct us to, and only if such information is required to provide you with specific services. We may use a credit card processing company to bill the users for the Service products or other charges. These third parties shall not retain, share or store any Personal Information except to provide these services and are bound by strict confidentiality agreements, which limit their use of such information.

University may disclose Personal Information to conform to legal requirements or to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other legal process received by University, whether or not a response is required by applicable law. 

University reserves the right to transfer Personal Information to a successor in interest that acquires rights to that information as a result of the sale of University or substantially all of its assets to that successor in interest. 

## How We Protect Your Information

All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions will be encrypted using SSL technology.

University shall use all and every commercially reasonable physical, managerial and technical safeguard to preserve the integrity and security of your Personal Information. We cannot warrant the security of any information you provide in the Service and you do so at your own risk. Once we received any information from you, University shall make all and every commercially reasonable effort to ensure the security of our systems. Please note that this is not a guarantee that unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors that may at any time compromise the security of user information, will not happen.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where you use a password for access to our Service, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. 

If you are registered as a user, we also enable you to view the data yourself and, if applicable, to delete or amend it. If incorrect information is stored despite our efforts to ensure that data is accurate and up to date, we will correct it at your request.

## Email Communications

University is committed to keeping your email address confidential. We shall never sell, rent or lease our user email lists or otherwise disclose the user email addresses to any third party. We shall use our users' email addresses exclusively to communicate University information to them. We respect your attention and time so we shall limit the frequency of our mailings to a reasonable amount.

University may email you service announcements such as day and time of expected interruptions of services, change of prices or service specifications. These emails have no opt-out status either.

## University marketing communications

University may email marketing messages such as product updates and special offers. However, these messages shall be sent only to University users and never to any third parties. Upon receipt of a University special offer or product update email message, users can opt out by clicking the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of the message.

## Children Under the Age of 13

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 13 ("Children"). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children have provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from Children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

## University administrative and service announcements 

University shall automatically email administrative messages such as "Thank you" messages or welcome messages introducing users to the University products and services, responses to password recovery, password and email change requests and similar explanatory messages that are necessary for user guidance. Users cannot opt-out from these emails.

## Changes in Our Privacy Policy

Your use of the Service, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Privacy Policy. University reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time and such modifications shall be effective upon posting them on the Website. You agree to be bound by any changes to this Privacy Policy when you use the Service after any such modification is posted. It is, therefore, important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated of any changes.

## Contacting University

If you have any questions or comments about our Privacy Policy please contact us at [certification@seo-training-course.com.](mailto:certification@seo-training-course.com.)

## GDPR Compliance Statement

On 25 May 2018, the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) replaces the existing 1995 EU Data Protection Directive (European Directive 95/46/EC). 

University is committed to GDPR compliance. We have evaluated the new requirements and restrictions imposed by the GDPR and reviewed where and how we collect, use, store and dispose of personal data. 

  * When processing data, we aim to ensure the following:

– The processing is lawful, fair and transparent
– The data is collected for a specific purpose and is necessary for the purpose
– The data must be accurate and kept up to date
– Data is not kept for longer than necessary
– The data is kept safe and secure

We may collect the following PII: email address, full name, billing address, credit card details, other billing details, phone number.

Our servers are located in the EU and in the USA.

We do care about the security of your data. University allows you to correct, amend, delete or limit the use of your Personal Data. All our third party service providers are GDPR compliant to ensure that your data are protected. We have takepropriate technical steps to ensure that we use the necessary level of protection for your information: 

  * Data encryption in transit (HTTPS, IPSec, TLS, PPTP, SSH)
  * Data encryption in our database
  * Logging of actions and log analysis
  * Password policy for access to the production database
  * Changing of internal passwords
  * Access control (physical and technical)
  * Limited access to the production database at the network level
  * Firewall
  * Antivirus
  * DDoS protection
  * PCS DSS compliance

You can call us at +0-800-404-8180 (UK toll-free) or email us at [certification@seo-training-course.com](mailto:certification@seo-training-course.com)
